Artem Shevelev

Full Stack Developer

Central Israel | 058-507-0892 | artem6evelev92@gmail.com

Github | LinkedIn

SUMMARY

Full-Stack Developer with a background in Business Development, Planning and Analysis. Experienced in JavaScript, React, Node.js. Possess strong skills in analyzing and solving complex problems that have helped me provide excellent tools to every management team that I've worked for. I know how to meet deadlines, work under pressure and handle multiple tasks. I am ready to quickly adapt to new situations and discover some interesting new fields.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Javascript, HTML5/CSS Frameworks: NodeJS, ReactJS, Bootstrap

Tools: jQuery, Git

Database: SQL(PostgreSQL, MySQL)

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

App Name - Github | Demo (add hyperlinks)

Brief description of the app's functionality and purpose

- Example: Utilized JSON Web Tokens and localStorage to store encrypted user information client-side.
- Action verb + what you did + result

App Name - Github | Demo (add hyperlinks)

Brief description of the app's functionality and purpose

- Action verb + what you did + result
- Action verb + what you did + result

EXPERIENCE

China Market Tour Operator

Tel-Aviv, Israel

Naftali Tours

March 2019 - Present

- Create a budget for incoming groups from China
- Establish business connections with Chinese travel companies, as a result per week 8-12 groups from China came to Israel
- Translate contracts from Chinese to English, as a result more than 10 signed contracts per year

CEO Harbin, China

Ideal International Kindergarten

November 2016 - May 2018

- Developed teaching methodology for Chinese children
- Lectured about the methodology in other schools and kindergartens
- Managed Chinese and foreign teachers

Sales Manager SiCheng YouXian Company Harbin, China

October 2015 - November 2016

Headed international sales department, won 2 contracts for wood industry supply

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development, JavaScript program

Tel-Aviv, Israel

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

April 2021 - June 2021

The Complete Web Developer in 2021: Zero to Mastery by Andrei Neagoie

Udemy Course October 2020 - December 2020

The Complete 2021 Web Development Bootcamp by Angela Yu

Udemy Course July 2020 - October 2020

TESOL CertificateGlobal TESOL Certificate Council
Beijing, China
January 2016 - May 2016

Bachelor Degree, International Trade and Economics

Harbin, China

Heilongjiang University

September 2011 - June 2016

LANGUAGES

English - fluent

Chinese - fluent

Hebrew - advanced

Russian - mother tongue